<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://blog.jannathomeo.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://blog.jannathomeo.org/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-02-20T10:33:54+06:00</updated><id>https://blog.jannathomeo.org/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Jannat Homeo .Org</title><subtitle>Jannat Homeo .Org offers effective Homeopathic treatment for deep seated diseases like Psoriasis, Respiratory Tract Infections, Infertility, PCOD, Asthma, Alopecia, Sexually Transmitted Diseases, Skin Disease, Fibroid, Tumour, etc.</subtitle><author><name>Dr. Md. Saju Ahmed</name><email>info.rahiq@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">What is the advantages of online consultation?</title><link href="https://blog.jannathomeo.org/2019/01/07/advantages-online-consultation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What is the advantages of online consultation?" /><published>2019-01-07T00:00:00+06:00</published><updated>2019-01-07T00:00:00+06:00</updated><id>https://blog.jannathomeo.org/2019/01/07/advantages-online-consultation</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.jannathomeo.org/2019/01/07/advantages-online-consultation/">&lt;p&gt;In one way or another, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jannathomeo.org/consultation/online-consultation.html&quot;&gt;online medical consultation&lt;/a&gt; has turned out to be a boon for people all over the globe. If you are hard pressed for time or you have to travel long distances to the clinic, you can simply ask your homeopathic doctor online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seeing a doctor online is an excellent option for those interested in a periodical consultation, looking for a follow-up examination or the chronically ill individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consulting a doctor is the first step for dealing with any ailment. Most of the consultation services that you will find online have been primarily conceived for helping people consult a doctor without leaving the comfort of their homes and discuss their problems in private. There are numerous benefits of this facility and it can be used by anyone. Some of the prominent perks of online doctor consultation are listed as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;First and foremost, you are able to get prompt medical attention. You are provided with an immediate response by an online doctor consultation service. However, they are not to be called in the case of emergency care. In normal situations, they will listen to your complaints and resolve the issue you are facing in a timely manner.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;One of the greatest perks of online doctor consultation is the availability of doctors round the clock. Like other online services, you can also get a medical consultation regardless of the hour. Thus, if you didn’t get the time to go to the clinic during the day, you can simply go for an online doctor consultation when you are free.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Healthcare can be quite costly and not everyone can afford the expense time and time again. Online doctor consultation is a great way to save some hard earned money that you spend on traveling, especially when the doctor is not nearby. In addition, you are provided with a number of services under one roof such as consultation, diagnosis, and follow-up, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Another reason why online doctor consultation is considered a convenient is that your medical records and history can be stored online and accessed for reference in the future. If you want, you can check details about primary care, the investigation reports and even the precautions you have been issued right from home. There is no need to call the doctor’s clinic anymore.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;When you are going for online doctor consultation, getting a second opinion is extremely easy and requires the minimal amount of fuss and effort. If the first consultation doesn’t satisfy you, it is easy to go for a second one at the same time and decide which one to go with.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;You don’t have to worry about geographical boundaries with the introduction of online doctor consultation. Now, you can get in touch with your doctor from anywhere in the world, no matter where they are. For instance, if a specialist resides in another country and it is cost prohibitive to go there, you can simply choose to consult online and get the best possible services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a nutshell, online doctor consultation is a great way of keeping yourself safe and healthy without much hassle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to know anything more than please send me an &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:rahi.hpathybd@gmail.com&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; anytime you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Dr. Md. Saju Ahmed&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Mobile: &lt;b&gt;+8801865738180.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://manage.xeonbd.com/aff.php?aff=325&amp;amp;page=defaultURL&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Domain and Web Hosting in BD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                        Flexible &amp;amp; Cheap Web Hosting&lt;br /&gt;                        SSD Shared Web Hosting Plan&lt;br /&gt;                        from USA &amp;amp; Bangladesh Data Center. 24x7 Help Desk&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Dr. Md. Saju Ahmed</name><email>info.rahiq@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html">In one way or another, online medical consultation has turned out to be a boon for people all over the globe. If you are hard pressed for time or you have to travel long distances to the clinic, you can simply ask your homeopathic doctor online.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">JHF managed recent social health service activity</title><link href="https://blog.jannathomeo.org/2019/01/06/jhf-recent-activity/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="JHF managed recent social health service activity" /><published>2019-01-06T00:00:00+06:00</published><updated>2019-01-06T00:00:00+06:00</updated><id>https://blog.jannathomeo.org/2019/01/06/jhf-recent-activity</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.jannathomeo.org/2019/01/06/jhf-recent-activity/">&lt;h2&gt;Recent activity of &lt;span class=&quot;caps&quot;&gt;Jannat Homeo Foundation&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently we start to serve our nationwide health care service. &lt;strong&gt;Jannat Homeo Clinic&lt;/strong&gt;, Munshiganj and &lt;strong&gt;Shefa Homeo Clinic&lt;/strong&gt;, Mymensingh jointly organized a &lt;strong&gt;Homeopathic Camp&lt;/strong&gt; at the date of &lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; December and &lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; December &lt;strong&gt;2018&lt;/strong&gt; at Taltola Madrasha and Bottola, Tarakandha, Mymensingh. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost 60 to 100 patients were visited per day and received there desired treatment. We serve there free of cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a snapshot of one of our activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/12-12-18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jannat Homeo Foundation Care&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Md. Saju Ahmed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://manage.xeonbd.com/aff.php?aff=325&amp;amp;page=managed-wordPress-ssd-hosting&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;SSD Powered Wordpress Hosting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                    For Unlimited Speed &amp;amp; Growth&lt;br /&gt;                    AI Powered Security, 30 Days Money Back&lt;br /&gt;                    24x7 Online Help Desk, 99.99% Uptime&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Find Us Here:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d3659.1888038494876!2d90.49916171436345!3d23.48970805460321!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x3755aec5e94a7919%3A0x271d9f81f7c998c7!2sAldi+Bazar%2C+Aldi+Bazar+Rd!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sbd!4v1456549121982&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;disqus_thread&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    /**
     *  RECOMMENDED CONFIGURATION VARIABLES: EDIT AND UNCOMMENT THE SECTION BELOW TO INSERT DYNAMIC VALUES FROM YOUR PLATFORM OR CMS.
     *  LEARN WHY DEFINING THESE VARIABLES IS IMPORTANT: https://disqus.com/admin/universalcode/#configuration-variables
     */
    /*
    var disqus_config = function () {
        this.page.url = PAGE_URL;  // Replace PAGE_URL with your page's canonical URL variable
        this.page.identifier = PAGE_IDENTIFIER; // Replace PAGE_IDENTIFIER with your page's unique identifier variable
    };
    */
    (function() {  // DON'T EDIT BELOW THIS LINE
        var d = document, s = d.createElement('script');
        
        s.src = '//drsaju.disqus.com/embed.js';
        
        s.setAttribute('data-timestamp', +new Date());
        (d.head || d.body).appendChild(s);
    })();
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;noscript&gt;Please enable JavaScript to view the &lt;a href=&quot;https://disqus.com/?ref_noscript&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;comments powered by Disqus.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;

&lt;script id=&quot;dsq-count-scr&quot; src=&quot;//drsaju.disqus.com/count.js&quot; async=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name>Dr. Md. Saju Ahmed</name><email>info.rahiq@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html">Recent activity of Jannat Homeo Foundation:</summary></entry></feed>